Cultural Survival Records MS180
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Indigenous and indigenous issues reference library, 1962 -- 2011; MS180.011; 42.0 Linear Feet
  - La Ruta del Papagayo (The Papagayo Route), 1993; MS180.011.045.00067 (Box 45)
  - La Tejedora-Newsletter of the Center for Traditional Textiles of Cusco, 2003 -- 2006; MS180.011.045.00068 (Box 45)
  - La Voz del Indio-Organo Oficial de los Pueblos Indios de Costa Rica (The Indian Voice-Official Organ of the Indian Peoples of Costa Rica), 1991; MS180.011.045.00069 (Box 45)
  - La Voz-The Monthly Magazine of the El Salvador Human Rights Commission, 1992 -- 1995; MS180.011.045.00070 (Box 45)
  - Labor Notes, 1999; MS180.011.045.00071 (Box 45)
  - Lac du Flambeau News-Wisconsin's Monthly Native newspaper, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.011.045.00072 (Box 45)
  - Lactation Review, 1979; MS180.011.045.00073 (Box 45)
  - Ladoc, 1989; MS180.011.045.00074 (Box 45)
  - Lagniappe Letter: Bi-Weekly Report of Issues Affecting Business in Latin America, 1987; MS180.011.045.00075 (Box 45)
  - Lake Baikal Region in the Twenty-First Centry: A Model of Sustainable Development or Continued Degradation?, 1993; MS180.011.045.00076 (Box 45)
  - Lakeland Times-The Voice of the Northwoods Since 1891, 1999; MS180.011.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - Land & People: A Pria Newsletter on People's Access to Natural Resources, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.011.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - Land & Rural Digest-The Record of Rural People's Policy, 1999; MS180.011.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - Land and Liberty: Economics, Politics, Philosophy, 1994; MS180.011.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - Land is Ours, 1997 -- 2000; MS180.011.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - Land Rights & Uranium, 1978; MS180.011.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - Land Rights for Indigenous and Tribal Peoples in Developing Countries, 1991; MS180.011.046.00007 (Box 46)
  - Land Rights News, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.011.046.00008 (Box 46)
  - Land Tenure Center Reprints, 1962 -- 1974; MS180.011.046.00009 (Box 46)
  - Land Tenure Center Workplan, 1967 -- 1993; MS180.011.046.00010 (Box 46)
  - Land Use Law Report, 1998; MS180.011.046.00011 (Box 46)
  - Landbokvinden I Danmark (The Woman Farmer in Denmark), MS180.011.046.00012 (Box 46)
  - Las Cuatro Estaciones-Mitologia y estructura social entre los U'wa, 1995; MS180.011.046.00013 (Box 46)
  - Las Mujeres del Campo y su Palabra (Country Women and their Words), 2002; MS180.011.046.00014 (Box 46)
  - LAS News, 1993 -- 1998; MS180.011.046.00015 (Box 46)
  - LASA Forum, 1982 -- 1987; MS180.011.046.00016 (Box 46)
  - Les Amérindiens de Guyane Française Aujourd'hui Éléments de Compréhension, 1979; MS180.011.046.00017 (Box 46)
  - Lateinamerika, 1988 -- 1990; MS180.011.046.00018 (Box 46)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean II: A Dissertation Bibliography, 1980; MS180.011.046.00019 (Box 46)
  - Latin America Regional Report: Mexico & Central America, 1981 -- 1982; MS180.011.046.00020 (Box 46)
  - Latin America Update, 1988; MS180.011.046.00021 (Box 46)
  - Latin America Weekly Report, 1980; MS180.011.046.00022 (Box 46)
  - Latin American Report, 1973 -- 1976; MS180.011.046.00023 (Box 46)
  - Latin American Special Reports, 1988; MS180.011.046.00024 (Box 46)
  - Latin American Studies, 1991 -- 1998; MS180.011.046.00025 (Box 46)
  - Latin American Studies Association XII International Congress, 1985; MS180.011.046.00026 (Box 46)
  - Latinamerica Press, 1983 -- 1998; MS180.011.046.00027 (Box 46)
  - Latinamericanist, 1986 -- 1990; MS180.011.046.00028 (Box 46)
  - Law Group Docket, 1993; MS180.011.046.00029 (Box 46)
  - Law Report, 1987; MS180.011.046.00030 (Box 46)
  - LAWASIA Human Rights Bulletin, 1984 -- 1987; MS180.011.046.00031 (Box 46)
  - Lawyer to Lawyer Network, 1994; MS180.011.046.00032 (Box 46)
  - Lawyers' Committee on Nuclear Policy, 1993; MS180.011.046.00033 (Box 46)
  - LDC Debt Report, 1991; MS180.011.046.00034 (Box 46)
  - Le Militant: Des Droits de L'homme [The Militant: The Human Rights], 1988; MS180.011.046.00035 (Box 46)
  - Leads, 1995; MS180.011.046.00036 (Box 46)
  - Leaf, 1992 -- 1993; MS180.011.046.00037 (Box 46)
  - Learning Alliance, 1997; MS180.011.046.00038 (Box 46)
  - Left Out? The Indians and the Canadian Constitution, MS180.011.046.00039 (Box 46)
  - Legitmacy of the United Nations: Towards an Enhanced Legal Status of non-State Actors, 1997; MS180.011.046.00040 (Box 46)
  - Letimaren, MS180.011.046.00041 (Box 46)
  - Letras Indigenas, 1994; MS180.011.046.00042 (Box 46)
  - Libertad, 1996; MS180.011.046.00043 (Box 46)
  - Libertas, 1992; MS180.011.046.00044 (Box 46)
  - Life & Human Rights, 1996 -- 1998; MS180.011.046.00045 (Box 46)
  - Life & Peace Institute, 1995; MS180.011.046.00046 (Box 46)
  - Life is Not Ours: Land and Human Rights in the Chittagong Hill Tracts Bangladesh, 1994; MS180.011.046.00047 (Box 46)
  - LIGHT Annual Report, 2003 -- 2004; MS180.011.046.00048 (Box 46)
  - Limi Sirpi Wihki Tangni Wal, 1992; MS180.011.046.00049 (Box 46)
  - Limitazione del Danno [Limiting the Damage], 1982; MS180.011.046.00050 (Box 46)
  - Linking Circles VI: Weaving a New Path in Philanthropy, 2007; MS180.011.046.00051 (Box 46)
  - Linking Macro and Micro: Setting Conservation Priorities the BCPP Way, 2001; MS180.011.046.00052 (Box 46)
  - Links: Health and Development Report, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.011.046.00053 (Box 46)
  - Listen Real Loud: News of Women's Liberation Worldwide, 1990 -- 1993; MS180.011.046.00054 (Box 46)
  - Livestock and Deforestation Central America in the 1980s and 1990s: A Policy Perspective, 1996; MS180.011.046.00055 (Box 46)
  - Lo'Il Maxil Yu'un Sk'op Ya'Yej Jlumaltik Voces de Chiapas II, 1996; MS180.011.046.00056 (Box 46)
  - Long March, 1991; MS180.011.046.00057 (Box 46)
  - Long Road Home: Angola's Post-War Inheritance, 1991; MS180.011.046.00058 (Box 46)
  - Longhouse of One Family: A Kinship Model of the Iroquoian Clan System, 1987; MS180.011.046.00059 (Box 46)
  - Look Before You Leap: What You Should Know About a North American Free Trade Agreement, 1991; MS180.011.046.00060 (Box 46)
  - Look Into Mauchak, MS180.011.046.00061 (Box 46)
  - Los Desaparecidos: Verdad, Justicia y Democracia [The Missing: Truth, Justice and Democracy], 1986; MS180.011.046.00062 (Box 46)
  - Lutheran World, 1980 -- 1983; MS180.011.046.00063 (Box 46)
  - Macuna: Portrait of a Culture, MS180.011.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - Madison Treaty Rights Support Group Newsletter, 1994 -- 1995; MS180.011.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - Magazin Dominical [Sunday Magazine], 1981; MS180.011.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - Mahogany Is Murder, 1992; MS180.011.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - Makitaak, 1991; MS180.011.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - Manitou Times, 1999; MS180.011.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - Manna, 1984; MS180.011.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - Manpower Report, 1963; MS180.011.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - Mansa, 2005 -- 2006; MS180.011.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - Margaret Mead, 1979; MS180.011.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Marketing Non-Timber Tropical Forest Products: Prospects and Promise - A Workshop Report, 1989; MS180.011.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Marri - Chichueu: Ten Times, We Will Overcome, 1986; MS180.011.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Marxist Leninist League of Tigray Publications, 1985; MS180.011.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Maryknoll, 1982 -- 1986; MS180.011.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Massacre in Beijing: The Events of 3-4 June 1989 and Their Aftermath, MS180.011.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Materiales de Trabajo 4 [Materials Work 4], 1984; MS180.011.047.00016 (Box 47)
  - Maternal Health: The Perennial Challenge, 1991; MS180.011.047.00017 (Box 47)
  - Maximum Yield? Sustainable Agriculture as a Tool for Conservation, 2001; MS180.011.047.00018 (Box 47)
  - Maya Educational Foundation, 2005; MS180.011.047.00019 (Box 47)
  - MCConnections, 1997; MS180.011.047.00020 (Box 47)
  - Medical Action Alert 53, 1996; MS180.011.047.00021 (Box 47)
  - Medical Anthropology, 1984; MS180.011.047.00022 (Box 47)
  - Medium Rare, 1993; MS180.011.047.00023 (Box 47)
  - Me-long, 1994; MS180.011.047.00024 (Box 47)
  - Memoria Lacandona [Lacandona Memory], 2000; MS180.011.047.00025 (Box 47)
  - Men-Tsee-Khang Newsletter, 1995 -- 1999; MS180.011.047.00026 (Box 47)
  - Mergen and His Friends A Nanai Folk Tale, 1989; MS180.011.047.00027 (Box 47)
  - Mesoamérica, 1996; MS180.011.047.00028 (Box 47)
  - Message Amérindien International, 1993; MS180.011.047.00029 (Box 47)
  - Metis Nation, 1985 -- 1986; MS180.011.047.00030 (Box 47)
  - Mexico Derechos Indigenas y Tenencia de la Tierra [Mexico Indigenous Rights and Land Tenure], 1991; MS180.011.047.00031 (Box 47)
  - Michigan Peace Team, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.011.047.00032 (Box 47)
  - Mid Atlantic Bulletin of Korean Studies, 1996; MS180.011.047.00033 (Box 47)
  - Midwest Pacifist Commentator, 1993; MS180.011.047.00034 (Box 47)
  - Migration Across Frontiers: Mexico and the United States, 1979; MS180.011.047.00035 (Box 47)
  - Migration Today, 1985; MS180.011.047.00036 (Box 47)
  - Migration World Magazine, 1988 -- 2002; MS180.011.047.00037 (Box 47)
  - Militarism Resource Project News, 1985; MS180.011.047.00038 (Box 47)
  - Milyen út vár rájuk? [The Gypsy Road], 1993 -- 1994; MS180.011.047.00039 (Box 47)
  - Mining, Minerals, and Sustainable Development Draft Report, 2002; MS180.011.047.00040 (Box 47)
  - Mink'a, 1977; MS180.011.047.00041 (Box 47)
  - Minority Organizations: A National Directory, 1992; MS180.011.047.00042 (Box 47)
  - Minority Rights Group International Publications, 1982 -- 2008; MS180.011.047.00043 (Box 47)
  - Minority Student Today: Recruitment, Retention, and Success, 1989; MS180.011.047.00044 (Box 47)
  - Minority Trendsetter, 1988 -- 1991; MS180.011.047.00045 (Box 47)
  - Misiva [Missive], 1988; MS180.011.047.00046 (Box 47)
  - Missiology, 1996; MS180.011.047.00047 (Box 47)
  - Mitigation at the La Grande Complex: A Review, 1994; MS180.011.047.00048 (Box 47)
  - M_p Kopehh_ix Hapo_ob __ba_ Apkt_ka, 2002; MS180.011.047.00049 (Box 47)
  - Modernization and National Minorities in China, 1979; MS180.011.047.00050 (Box 47)
  - Mon National Relief Committee: Monthly Report, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.011.047.00051 (Box 47)
  - Monday Developments, 1984; MS180.011.047.00052 (Box 47)
  - Montreal Institute for Genocide and Human Rights Studies Publications, 1989 -- 1993; MS180.011.047.00053 (Box 47)
  - More than a Token Gesture, 1979; MS180.011.047.00054 (Box 47)
  - Mount Graham Coalition Action Alert, 1993; MS180.011.047.00055 (Box 47)
  - Mozambique Support Network Newsletter, 1990 -- 1991; MS180.011.047.00056 (Box 47)
  - Mr. Cognito - Human Rights Issue, 1987; MS180.011.047.00057 (Box 47)
  - Mujer Popular, 2000 -- 2001; MS180.011.047.00058 (Box 47)
  - Multilateral Treaty Frameworks, 2002; MS180.011.047.00059 (Box 47)
  - Multinationals: New Approaches to Agricultural and Rural Development, 1981; MS180.011.047.00060 (Box 47)
  - Nagao Natural Environment Foundation Newsletter, 1996; MS180.011.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - Narcotics Intelligence Estimate, 1983; MS180.011.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - Narraciones Bocotas (Dialectro de Chiriqui), 1992; MS180.011.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - Narrativa Argentina [Argentina Narrative], 1989 -- 1996; MS180.011.048.00004 (Box 48)
  - NASSA News, 1982; MS180.011.048.00005 (Box 48)
  - Nation [1 of 8], 1998 -- 2000; MS180.011.048.00006 (Box 48)
  - Nation [2 of 8], 2003; MS180.011.048.00007 (Box 48)
  - Nation [3 of 8], 2005; MS180.011.048.00008 (Box 48)
  - Nation [4 of 8], 2006; MS180.011.048.00009 (Box 48)
  - Nation [5 of 8], 2007; MS180.011.048.00010 (Box 48)
  - National Aboriginal Conference Newsletter, 1980 -- 1982; MS180.011.048.00011 (Box 48)
  - National Aboriginal Directory, 1991; MS180.011.048.00012 (Box 48)
  - National Boycott Newsletter, 1987; MS180.011.048.00013 (Box 48)
  - National Forest Management in the American Tropics, 1991; MS180.011.048.00014 (Box 48)
  - National Legal Conference on Immigration and Refugee Policy (22nd Annual), 1999; MS180.011.048.00015 (Box 48)
  - National Reporter, 1985 -- 1987; MS180.011.048.00016 (Box 48)
  - National Workshop of Indigenous Peoples on Human Rights - Proceedings, 2004; MS180.011.048.00017 (Box 48)
  - Native American Resource Center, 1998; MS180.011.048.00018 (Box 48)
  - Native American Rights Fund Annual Report, 1981; MS180.011.048.00019 (Box 48)
  - Native Brazilians in São Paulo, 1999; MS180.011.048.00020 (Box 48)
  - Native Business Summit Review, 1986; MS180.011.049.00001 (Box 49)
  - Native Issues, 1987; MS180.011.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - Native Nations, 1991; MS180.011.049.00003 (Box 49)
  - Native Press, 1996; MS180.011.049.00004 (Box 49)
  - Native Studies Review, 1995; MS180.011.049.00005 (Box 49)
  - Natural Resources in Latin America, 1983; MS180.011.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - NCC Review, 2009; MS180.011.049.00007 (Box 49)
  - NCHR, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.011.049.00008 (Box 49)
  - NDI Civic Update, 1999; MS180.011.049.00009 (Box 49)
  - neighbor to neighbor Nation to Nation, 2001; MS180.011.049.00010 (Box 49)
  - Neighborhood Caretaker, 1985 -- 1987; MS180.011.049.00011 (Box 49)
  - Neighbors, 1986; MS180.011.049.00012 (Box 49)
  - Netherlands Center for Indigenous Peoples Annual Report, 2004; MS180.011.049.00013 (Box 49)
  - Netherlands Quarterly, 1990 -- 1992; MS180.011.049.00014 (Box 49)
  - New Directions for Women, 1988; MS180.011.049.00015 (Box 49)
  - New England Nonprofit Quarterly, 1998; MS180.011.049.00016 (Box 49)
  - New Ground, 1990 -- 1991; MS180.011.049.00017 (Box 49)
  - New Internationalist, 1988 -- 1998; MS180.011.049.00018 (Box 49)
  - New Wilderness Letter, 1978 -- 1980; MS180.011.049.00019 (Box 49)
  - Newest Americans, 1987; MS180.011.049.00020 (Box 49)
  - News from Aprovecho, 1986; MS180.011.049.00021 (Box 49)
  - News from Brazil, 1993; MS180.011.049.00022 (Box 49)
  - News from ECOSOC, 2002; MS180.011.049.00023 (Box 49)
  - News from Indian Country, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.011.049.00024 (Box 49)
  - News from MCLI, 1991; MS180.011.049.00025 (Box 49)
  - News from Native California, 1997; MS180.011.049.00026 (Box 49)
  - Newsletter from the Sierra Madre, 1985 -- 1998; MS180.011.049.00027 (Box 49)
  - Newsletter of the 50th Anniversary of the United Nations, 1994 -- 1995; MS180.011.049.00028 (Box 49)
  - Newsletter of the Middle East, 1989 -- 1994; MS180.011.049.00029 (Box 49)
  - Newsletter Panapana, 1987; MS180.011.049.00030 (Box 49)
  - NewSpaces, 1998; MS180.011.049.00031 (Box 49)
  - NewsTibet, 1990 -- 2002; MS180.011.049.00032 (Box 49)
  - NewsWatch Publications, 1997 -- 1998; MS180.011.049.00033 (Box 49)
  - NGLS Roundup, 1998; MS180.011.049.00034 (Box 49)
  - NGO Directory: Tropical Forest and Multilateral Development Bank Campaigns, 1988; MS180.011.049.00035 (Box 49)
  - NGO Networker, 1990 -- 1992; MS180.011.049.00036 (Box 49)
  - NGO Reporter, 1999 -- 2005; MS180.011.049.00037 (Box 49)
  - Ngurrju Maninja Kurlangu: Nyurnu Yapa Kurlangu [Bush Medicine], 1980; MS180.011.049.00038 (Box 49)
  - Nicaragua, 1982; MS180.011.049.00039 (Box 49)
  - Nicaragua Network News, 1980 -- 1987; MS180.011.049.00040 (Box 49)
  - Nicaragua: An Environmental Perspective, MS180.011.049.00041 (Box 49)
  - Nicaragua: An Eye-witness Report on the Electoral Process, 1984; MS180.011.049.00042 (Box 49)
  - Nicaragua: Another View, 1987; MS180.011.049.00043 (Box 49)
  - Nicaraguan Developments, 1993; MS180.011.049.00044 (Box 49)
  - Nicaragua's Human Rights Record, 1983; MS180.011.049.00045 (Box 49)
  - Nimuendaju, 1979; MS180.011.049.00046 (Box 49)
  - Nishnawbe-Aski Resource Development, MS180.011.049.00047 (Box 49)
  - Nitassinan News, 1998; MS180.011.049.00048 (Box 49)
  - NMAI Runner, 1997 -- 1998; MS180.011.049.00049 (Box 49)
  - Nomadic News, 2001 -- 2005; MS180.011.049.00050 (Box 49)
  - Nomos: Studies in Spontaneous Order, 1991; MS180.011.050.00001 (Box 50)
  - Non-Profit Times, 1990; MS180.011.050.00002 (Box 50)
  - Nonviolent Activist, 1996 -- 2000; MS180.011.050.00003 (Box 50)
  - Nonviolent Sanctions, 1992; MS180.011.050.00004 (Box 50)
  - Norbu: Education & Culture in Tibet, MS180.011.050.00005 (Box 50)
  - Nordiska Afrikainstiutet Publications, 2001; MS180.011.050.00006 (Box 50)
  - North Country Prout Journal, 1985; MS180.011.050.00007 (Box 50)
  - Northeast Corner, 1987; MS180.011.050.00008 (Box 50)
  - Northern Line, 1991; MS180.011.050.00009 (Box 50)
  - Northstar News and Analysis, 1990 -- 1992; MS180.011.050.00010 (Box 50)
  - Northwest Tribal Transportation News, 1999; MS180.011.050.00011 (Box 50)
  - Not Development, But Theft: The Testimony of Penan Communities in Sarawak, 2000; MS180.011.050.00012 (Box 50)
  - Noticias Antropológicas [Anthropoligical News], 1988; MS180.011.050.00013 (Box 50)
  - Nowhere to Turn: Failure to Protect, Support, and Assure Justice for Darfuri Women, 2009; MS180.011.050.00014 (Box 50)
  - NRDC Tropical Moist Forests Conservation Bulletin, 1978 -- 1979; MS180.011.050.00015 (Box 50)
  - Nuclear Roulette: The Case Against a "Nuclear Renaissance", 2011; MS180.011.050.00016 (Box 50)
  - Nuclear Technology from West Germany: A Case of Disharmony in US-Brazilian Relations, 1978; MS180.011.050.00017 (Box 50)
  - Nunalu Imaklu [Land & Water], 1997 -- 1998; MS180.011.050.00018 (Box 50)
  - Nunatsiaqnews, 1998 -- 1999; MS180.011.050.00019 (Box 50)
  - Nutrition Health Review, 1986; MS180.011.050.00020 (Box 50)
  - O Debate Sobre A Educação Indígena No Brasil (1975-1995)(The Debate About Indigenous Education in Brazil 1975-1995, MS180.011.050.00021 (Box 50)
  - Obychasyshinehenskieburiyati, MS180.011.050.00022 (Box 50)
  - Oceania Papua New Guinea, 1997; MS180.011.050.00023 (Box 50)
  - Oh-Toh-Kin: Publications for/of Native People's Resistance, 1992 -- 1994; MS180.011.050.00024 (Box 50)
  - Ojarasca (1 of 2), 1993 -- 1994; MS180.011.050.00025 (Box 50)
  - Ojarasca (2 of 2), 1991 -- 1993; MS180.011.050.00026 (Box 50)
  - Oklahoma Colorado-West Indies, 2002; MS180.011.050.00027 (Box 50)
  - Ökozidmagazine, 1990; MS180.011.050.00028 (Box 50)
  - Omaere: Boletin del Parque Pedagogico Etnobotanico Omaere (Omaere: Boletin of the Omaere Pedagogical Ethnobotanical Park), 1997 -- 1999; MS180.011.050.00029 (Box 50)
  - On Beyond War, 1989; MS180.011.050.00030 (Box 50)
  - On Indian Land: Support for Native Sovereignty, 1995 -- 1996; MS180.011.050.00031 (Box 50)
  - Oneida Indian Nation: Pictures of Progess, MS180.011.050.00032 (Box 50)
  - Onkwarihwa'shon:'a [Our Affairs], 1993; MS180.011.050.00033 (Box 50)
  - OPAN, 1986 -- 1989; MS180.011.050.00034 (Box 50)
  - Operating Policy on Women in Development, 1987; MS180.011.050.00035 (Box 50)
  - Operation Crossroads Africa 2000 Program Application, MS180.011.050.00036 (Box 50)
  - Opinião [Opinion], 1973 -- 1975; MS180.011.050.00037 (Box 50)
  - Orang Asli Assistance Fund Newsletter, 1998; MS180.011.050.00038 (Box 50)
  - Orang Asli Studies Newsletter, 1987 -- 1989; MS180.011.050.00039 (Box 50)
  - Orçamento & Política Ambiental (Budget and Environment Policy), 2002 -- 2007; MS180.011.050.00040 (Box 50)
  - Organic Food Guide for Massachusetts, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.011.051.00001; NOFA (Box 51)
  - Oriental Rug Review: A Bimonthly Journal of Oriental Rugs and Other Textiles, 1993; MS180.011.051.00002; Oriental Rug Review (Box 51)
  - Oriental Rug Review: A Monthly Review of Oriental Rugs and Rug Literature for the Collector, 1984; MS180.011.051.00003; Oriental Rug Review (Box 51)
  - Origin, Evolution, and Diffusion of Coca, Erythroxylum spp., in South and Central America, 1984; MS180.011.051.00004; Papers of the Peabody Museum of Archaeology and Ethnology (Box 51)
  - Orinoco Indígena, 1991; MS180.011.051.00005; Guayana Consejo de Redaccion [Guiana Drafting Council] (Box 51)
    The Indigenous Orinoco
  - Oromo Liberation Front Publications, 1978 -- 1988; MS180.011.051.00006; Oromo Liberation Front (Box 51)
  - Our Challenge: Voices for Peace, Partnerships and Renewal Final Report, 2005; MS180.011.051.00007; United Nations (Box 51)
  - Our Land, Our Right: Aboriginal Land Rights in Australia's Northern Territory, 1991; MS180.011.051.00008; Central Land Council; Northern Land Council (Box 51)
  - Our Search, 1990; MS180.011.051.00009; Central American Association of Relatives of Detained Dissappeared (Box 51)
  - Ouroboros, 1998 -- 2000; MS180.011.051.00010; The Goldman Environmental Prize (Box 51)
  - Outlook, 1999; MS180.011.051.00011; Hathway Investments Ltd. (Box 51)
  - Outsider: The Newsletter of Minority Rights Group International, 1998; MS180.011.051.00012; Minority Rights Group International (Box 51)
  - Overcoming Indigenous Disadvantages, 2009; MS180.011.051.00013; Commonwealth of Australia (Box 51)
  - Oxfam America Project Report, MS180.011.051.00014; Oxfam America (Box 51)
  - Pachamama Alliance, 2003; MS180.011.051.00015; The Pachamama Alliance (Box 51)
  - Pacific News Bulletin, 1997 -- 2005; MS180.011.051.00016; Nuclear Free and Independent Pacific Movement (Box 51)
  - Palabra dulce, aire de vida, MS180.011.051.00017; The National Colombian Authority for Indigenous Government (ONIC) (Box 51)
    Sweet Words, Breath of Life
  - Panamá: Cómo potenciar a las mujeres indigenas para que protejan y comercialicen mejor sus artesanías, 2005; MS180.011.051.00018; OMP (Box 51)
    Panama: How to Empower Indigenous Women to Better Protect and Market Their Crafts
  - Panchar Penemu, 1993; MS180.011.051.00019; Institute for Community Education (IPK) (Box 51)
    Radiate Knowledge
  - Panda, 1992; MS180.011.051.00020; ADENA/WWF (Box 51)
  - Panewa, 1988 -- 1991; MS180.011.051.00021; Conselho Indigenista Missionário [Indigenous Missionary Council] (Box 51)
  - Panoscope, 1992; MS180.011.051.00022; The Panos Institute (Box 51)
  - Papers on Latin America, 1989 -- 1990; MS180.011.051.00023; Columbia University - The Institute of Latin American and Iberian Studies (Box 51)
  - Parab Licas, 1994 -- 1999; MS180.011.051.00024; Instituto Socioambiental (Box 51)
  - Parabola, 2009; MS180.011.051.00025 (Box 51)
  - Paradise Lost: The Suppression of Environmental Rights and Freedom of Expression in Burma, 1994; MS180.011.051.00026; ARTICLE 19 (Box 51)
  - Parlimentary Speeches Making the Anniversary of the Aboriginal Referendum of 27 May 1967, 1992; MS180.011.051.00027; Aboriginal and Torres Strait Commission (Box 51)
  - Participatory Learning and Action: Mapping for Change - Practice, Technologies and Communication, 2006; MS180.011.051.00028; International Institute for Environment and Development (Box 51)
  - Partido Verde, 1990; MS180.011.051.00029; Partido Verde [Green Party] (Box 51)
    Green Party
  - Partners, 1993 -- 1995; MS180.011.051.00030; Partners of the Americas (Box 51)
  - Passtoors Trial: A Report to the ICJ and the NJCM On a Treason Trial in South Africa, 1986; MS180.011.051.00031; Nederlands Juristen Comite Voor de Mensenrechten (NJCM) [Dutch Section of the International Commission of Jurists] (Box 51)
  - Pathways: Growing Philanthrophy in Indian Country, 2008; MS180.011.051.00032; The Center on Philanthropy at Indiana University (Box 51)
  - Paving Moratorium Update, 1993 -- 1994; MS180.011.051.00033; Fossil Fuels Policy Action Institute (Box 51)
  - PBI/USA REPORT, 1995 -- 1999; MS180.011.051.00034; Peace Brigades International/USA (Box 51)
  - Peace International, 1984; MS180.011.051.00035; International Peace Committee (Box 51)
  - Peace Matters, 2000; MS180.011.051.00036; Hague Appeal for Peace (Box 51)
  - Peace News, 2003; MS180.011.051.00037; Campaign Against Arms Trade (Box 51)
  - PEEReview, 1998; MS180.011.051.00038; Public Employees for Environmental Responsibility (Box 51)
  - Pensamiento Propio, 1985 -- 1986; MS180.011.051.00039; Instituto de Investigaciones Economicas y Sociales (INIES) [Institute of Economics and Social Research] (Box 51)
    Individual Ideas
  - People, 1980; MS180.011.051.00040; International Planned Parenthood Federation (Box 51)
  - People & the Planet, 1986; MS180.011.051.00041; World Wide Fund for Nature (WWF) (Box 51)